{
    "id": "38_Entertainment_668",
    "claim": "For  years, the tycoon led Miss Universe. One of the winners accused him of harassment and humiliationBetween the scenes of the female beauty contests often inhabits a world of mixed egos, innocent illusions and sinuous bodies seeking notoriety at all costs. The environment always dreamed of by a narcissistic billionaire, obsessed with women and physical grace. In , Donald Trump bought Miss Universe's organization for  millions of dollars, moving on to controlling Miss Universe, Miss USA contests. USA. and Miss Teen EE. USA. In these contests it is about seeking beauty, the maximum beauty that exists: that of a woman, then declared the magnate. Trump's acquisition of the competition coincided with the election of Alicia Machado, Miss Venezuela in , as Miss Universe. A crown for poisoned dessert. Machado, a bell of brown hair and penetrating gaze, was at that time #NUMBER* years old, weighed #NUMBER* kilos and took the first steps of an incipient, but promising career on the catwalk. In a matter of months his ambitions were frustrated. His biggest mistake?According to Trump, getting fat  kilos when he was still wearing the most beautiful woman crown in the universe. New York billionaire angered and publicly humiliated her. He accompanied her personally to a gymnasium in the Big Apple, where she had summoned  journalists, to sweat her shirt and start a fight against her weight. He's someone who likes to eat. No doubt, Trump said. This brutal attack plunged her into deep depression. I was sick.. I had anorexia and bulimia for five years, told the Venezuelan in an interview with The New York Times last May. Machado also had to endure being ridiculed by referring to her as Miss Piggy (Miss Pig) and Miss Housekeeping (Miss Housewife) for being Latina. Alicia Machado and Donald Trump in - ABCTrump had no objection to recognizing that he was pushing her to lose weight, arguing that keeping her in excellent shape was her obligation as Miss Universe. Democrat contender Hillary Clinton took Machado out as a visible face of Trump's macho attitude during the first presidential debate. Far from retreating, the Republican continued to attack Machado, who last summer obtained U.S. citizenship. Did corrupt Clinton help disgusting Alicia M?. to become an American citizen to be able to use it in the debate?, Trump asked himself in a tweet. Over the past few months, Alicia defended Clinton to an extreme extent. On Wednesday, after learning about the nightmare of defeat, she contacted her via telephone to express her support. I talked to her, she thanked me for supporting her in this campaign. I didn't even look for him and they didn't look for me. I came by chance, and I'm still very firm with my position, he told Televisa. Trump's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants also scotched on many of the beauty queens of Latin origin. Lupita Jones, former Miss Universe of Mexico, announced that her country would not participate in . Former Miss Universe Zuleyka Rivera of Puerto Rico retired from the Miss USA jury. USA. and the Colombian Paulina Vega, Miss Universe , called her speech unfair and harmful. However, not all of them whipped up their godfather. Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete closed ranks around the owner of the contest. My working relationship with Trump has always been very good. I can't tell you if he did wrong or well, he deserves all my respect. Those who did take letters in the matter after the attack on the Mexicans were the NBC networks, which cancelled the transmission of the contest, and Univision and Televisa who also broke professional ties with him. In September , still a Republican candidate, sold the company that organizes Miss Universe to the entertainment event company WME/IMG. ABC has tried to get in touch with them, but they have declined to make any statement about Trump. Surprisingly, the transaction took place only three days after the mogul bought from the NBC chain the part that did not yet own that company, becoming the sole owner. I enjoyed being the owner of the Miss Universe, Miss USA. U.S. and Miss Teen USA. USA. When I got them, they were in serious trouble. It has been an honor to make them a world success, he said in a statement. Trump turned away from beauty competitions to take on a much more ambitious new job; leading the most powerful country in the universe. Back then, only he knew. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.abc.es",
    "date": "25/09/2017",
    "veracity": 1,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "I  years, the tycoon led Miss Universe .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who led Miss Universe?",
                    "answer": "the tycoon"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who led Miss Universe in 2017?",
                    "score": 0.7922,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that I   years , the tycoon led Miss Universe|ROOT\tthat I   years , the tycoon led Miss Universe|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the person that led Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.7215,
                    "answers": "the tycoon|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.7201,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat I|nmod\tthat I  |dep\tyears|npadvmod\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.6843,
                    "answers": "Miss|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Trump One of the winners I Televisa harassment Trump's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants female beauty contests often the beauty queens of Latin origin , Lupita Jones, former Miss Universe of Mexico her at all Mexico .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Lupita Jones' nationality?",
                    "answer": "beauty queens of Latin origin"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Trump's comments on Mexican women beauty contests?",
                    "score": 0.6867,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj\t's|case\ton Mexican immigrants female beauty contests often the beauty queens of Latin origin|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Trump's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants?",
                    "score": 0.6854,
                    "answers": "Trump 's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants female beauty contests often the beauty queens of Latin origin|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Trump and Mexican beauty queens?",
                    "score": 0.6477,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Trump One of the winners I Televisa harassment Trump 's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants female beauty contests often the beauty queens of Latin origin , Lupita Jones , former Miss Universe of Mexico her at all Mexico|ROOT\ton 25/09/2017|prep\txenophobic|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who are the beauty queens of Latin origin?",
                    "score": 0.6341,
                    "answers": "Mexican immigrants female beauty contests often the beauty queens of Latin origin|pobj\toften the beauty queens of Latin origin|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the origin of Lupita Jones?",
                    "score": 0.6255,
                    "answers": "of Latin origin|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Mexico environment always dreamed of her a narcissistic billionaire, obsessed with women and physical grace.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say that Mexico environment always dreamed of her a narcissistic billionaire?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a billionaire and a billionaire?",
                    "score": 0.7021,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Mexico environment always dreamed of her a narcissistic billionaire , obsessed with women and physical grace|ROOT\ton 25/09/2017|prep\tMexico environment|nsubj\talways|advmod\tthat Mexico environment always dreamed of her a narcissistic billionaire , obsessed with women and physical grace|ccomp\tof her a narcissistic billionaire , obsessed with women and physical grace|prep\ta|det\tnarcissistic|amod\ther a narcissistic billionaire , obsessed with women and physical grace|pobj\tobsessed with women and physical grace|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the physical grace of a billionaire?",
                    "score": 0.6587,
                    "answers": "physical grace|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the billionaire that is obsessed with women and physical grace?",
                    "score": 0.6509,
                    "answers": "that|mark\ther|nmod\t,|punct\tand|cc"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In , the tycoon her Miss Universe Trump for  millions of dollars, moving on to controlling Miss Universe not all of them USA contests.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did the tycoon her Miss Universe Trump for millions of dollars?",
                    "answer": "In"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many USA contests has Miss Universe Trump controlled?",
                    "score": 0.8014,
                    "answers": "not all of them USA contests|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How much money did Miss Universe Trump receive for controlling Miss Universe not all of them USA contests?",
                    "score": 0.8008,
                    "answers": "of dollars|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Miss Universe Trump?",
                    "score": 0.6988,
                    "answers": "the tycoon her Miss Universe Trump|nsubj\tMiss|compound\ther Miss Universe|compound\ther Miss Universe Trump|appos\tthat In , the tycoon her Miss Universe Trump for|ccomp\tMiss|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Miss Universe Trump?",
                    "score": 0.6872,
                    "answers": "her|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Miss Universe and Miss Universe Trump?",
                    "score": 0.687,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that In , the tycoon her Miss Universe Trump for   millions of dollars , moving on to controlling Miss Universe not all of them USA contests|ROOT\tthat|mark\tIn|dep\t,|punct\tthe|det\t,|punct\t, moving on to controlling Miss Universe not all of them USA contests|ccomp\ton|prt\tto controlling Miss Universe not all of them USA contests|prep\tcontrolling Miss Universe not all of them USA contests|pcomp\tnot|neg\tof them|prep\tthem|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.abc.es say that I was a member of the BBC?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the ABC news website?",
                    "score": 0.6925,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that I|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does ABC.es do?",
                    "score": 0.6918,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the names of the person who committed the act?",
                    "score": 0.6348,
                    "answers": "that|mark"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say that I Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where is I Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete from?",
                    "score": 0.7958,
                    "answers": "Mexicana|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Ximena Navarrete?",
                    "score": 0.7096,
                    "answers": "Ximena|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete?",
                    "answer": "Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete?",
                    "score": 0.7409,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj\twww.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete|ROOT\ton 25/09/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tMiss|compound\tUniverso|compound\tXimena|compound\tthat Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete about seeking beautyI Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete Democrat contender Hillary Clinton of her , then I the tycoon .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Democrat candidate for Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete?",
                    "answer": "Hillary Clinton of her"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete?",
                    "score": 0.6461,
                    "answers": "Democrat contender Hillary Clinton of her|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Trump the tycoon acquisition of Miss Universe the first presidential debate election of Alicia MachadoTrump in , as Miss her .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the tycoon who won the first presidential debate?",
                    "answer": "Alicia MachadoTrump in"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did Trump buy Miss Universe from?",
                    "score": 0.7641,
                    "answers": "of Alicia MachadoTrump|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was Miss Universe in the first presidential debate?",
                    "score": 0.6804,
                    "answers": "presidential debate|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Trump and Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.6657,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj\tthat|mark\tTrump the tycoon acquisition of Miss Universe|nsubj\tthe|det\tthe tycoon|compound\tthe tycoon acquisition of Miss Universe|appos\tthe|det\tthat Trump the tycoon acquisition of Miss Universe the first presidential debate election of Alicia MachadoTrump in , as Miss her|ccomp\tin ,|prep\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.6634,
                    "answers": "of Miss Universe|prep\tMiss|compound\tMiss Universe|pobj\tAlicia|compound\tas Miss her|prep\tMiss|compound\tMiss her|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.6591,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Trump the tycoon acquisition of Miss Universe the first presidential debate election of Alicia MachadoTrump in , as Miss her|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "her Trump's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say that Trump's comments on Mexican immigrants were xenophobic?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did ABC.es say about Trump's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants?",
                    "score": 0.8541,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that her Trump 's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are Trump's views on Mexican immigrants?",
                    "score": 0.8505,
                    "answers": "her Trump 's|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Trump's stance on Mexican immigrants?",
                    "score": 0.8322,
                    "answers": "that|mark\ther|poss\ton Mexican immigrants|prep\tMexican immigrants|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "her NBC Democrat contender Hillary Clinton One of the winners her the contest an American citizen , weighed Televisa NUMBER* an American citizen the first presidential debate Trump steps I Trump , but I .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who weighed Televisa NUMBER*?",
                    "answer": "an American citizen"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who weighed Televisa NUMBER*?",
                    "answer": "an American citizen"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Hillary Clinton weigh during the first debate?",
                    "score": 0.7259,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that her NBC Democrat contender Hillary Clinton One of the winners her the contest an American citizen , weighed Televisa NUMBER * an American citizen the first presidential debate Trump steps I Trump , but I|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Trump and Televisa?",
                    "score": 0.6588,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj\ton 25/09/2017|prep\tthat|mark\ther|poss\tHillary|compound\tOne of the winners her the contest an American citizen|appos\tof the winners|prep\tthe|det\tthe winners|pobj\ther|nmod\tthe|det\ther the contest|appos\tan|det\t,|punct\tthat her NBC Democrat contender Hillary Clinton One of the winners her the contest an American citizen , weighed Televisa NUMBER * an American citizen the first presidential debate Trump steps I Trump , but I|ccomp\tTelevisa NUMBER * an American citizen the first presidential debate Trump steps I Trump , but I|dobj\t*|punct\tan|det\tthe|det\tpresidential|amod\tthe first presidential debate|dep\tsteps|dep\tTrump steps I|dep\tthe first presidential debate Trump steps I Trump , but I|appos\t,|punct\tbut|cc\tI|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Televisa's immigration status?",
                    "score": 0.6368,
                    "answers": "an American citizen|appos\tan American citizen|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the company that organizes Miss Universe frustrated.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say that the company that organizes Miss Universe was frustrated?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who runs Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.8165,
                    "answers": "In the company that organizes Miss Universe|prep\tthe company that organizes Miss Universe|pobj\tthat organizes Miss Universe|relcl\tMiss|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who runs the company that organizes Miss Universe frustrated?",
                    "score": 0.796,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that In the company that organizes Miss Universe frustrated|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the entertainment event company WME/IMG the tycoon , getting fat  kilos Democrat contender Hillary Clinton One of the winners was the entertainment event company WME/IMG wearing the her beautiful woman crown in her universe.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the tycoon who won a contest on 25/09/2017?",
                    "answer": "the tycoon"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of Hillary Clinton's crown?",
                    "score": 0.5345,
                    "answers": "wearing the her beautiful woman crown in her universe|advcl\tthe her beautiful woman crown|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is WME/IMG the tycoon?",
                    "score": 0.5317,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj\twww.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that the entertainment event company WME / IMG the tycoon , getting fat   kilos Democrat contender Hillary Clinton One of the winners was the entertainment event company WME / IMG wearing the her beautiful woman crown in her universe|ROOT\ton 25/09/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tentertainment event|compound\tthe entertainment event company WME / IMG the tycoon|nsubj\tWME|nmod\t/|punct\tthe|det\tthe tycoon|appos\t,|punct\tthe entertainment event company WME / IMG the tycoon , getting fat|ccomp\tfat|acomp\tthat the entertainment event company WME / IMG the tycoon , getting fat   kilos|dep\tkilos|dobj\tHillary|compound\tOne of the winners|nsubj\tof the winners|prep\tthe|det\tthe winners|pobj\tDemocrat contender Hillary Clinton One of the winners was the entertainment event company WME / IMG wearing the her beautiful woman crown in her universe|ccomp\tthe|det\tentertainment event|compound\tthe entertainment event company WME / IMG|attr\tWME|nmod\t/|punct\tthe|det\ther|poss\tbeautiful|amod\tbeautiful woman|compound\ther|poss\ther universe|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is WME/IMG?",
                    "score": 0.5064,
                    "answers": "WME / IMG|appos\tDemocrat contender Hillary Clinton|nsubj\tWME / IMG|appos\tin her universe|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is WME/IMG?",
                    "score": 0.5035,
                    "answers": "entertainment|compound\tentertainment|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the tycoon sold and publicly humiliated One of the winners .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say that the tycoon sold and publicly humiliated one of the winners?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the winner of The Apprentice in 2017?",
                    "score": 0.7607,
                    "answers": "One of the winners|dobj\tof the winners|prep\tthe winners|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who did the tycoon sell and publicly humiliated?",
                    "score": 0.7463,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tand|cc\tpublicly|advmod\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the owner of the property that the tycoon sold and publicly humiliated one of the winners?",
                    "score": 0.7258,
                    "answers": "the tycoon|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the man that was sold and publicly humiliated?",
                    "score": 0.5998,
                    "answers": "that the tycoon sold and publicly humiliated One of the winners|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the tycoon Trump One of the winners personally NBC a gymnasium in the Big Apple, where One of the winners the company that organizes Miss Universe  journalists, to sweat shirt and start a fight against weight.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who organizes Miss Universe journalists?",
                    "answer": "NBC"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who organized the Miss Universe pageant?",
                    "score": 0.697,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that the tycoon Trump One of the winners personally NBC a gymnasium in the Big Apple , where One of the winners the company that organizes Miss Universe   journalists , to sweat shirt and start a fight against weight|ROOT\ton 25/09/2017|prep\twhere One of the winners the company that organizes Miss Universe   journalists|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who organized Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.6908,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tthe tycoon Trump One of the winners|nsubj\tOne of the winners|appos\tof the winners|prep\tthe|det\tthe winners|pobj\tpersonally|advmod\ta|det\tin the Big Apple|prep\tthe|det\tBig|compound\t,|punct\twhere|advmod\tof the winners|prep\tthe|det\tthe winners|pobj\tthe|det\tthe company that organizes Miss Universe|appos\tthat|nsubj\tthat organizes Miss Universe|relcl\tMiss|nmod\tjournalists|dobj\t,|punct\tto|aux\tand|cc\ta|det\tagainst weight|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What type of shirt did the Miss Universe team wear?",
                    "score": 0.659,
                    "answers": "shirt|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the gymnasium that Trump attended?",
                    "score": 0.6049,
                    "answers": "that the tycoon Trump One of the winners personally NBC a gymnasium in the Big Apple , where One of the winners the company that organizes Miss Universe   journalists , to sweat shirt and start a fight against weight|ccomp\ta gymnasium in the Big Apple , where One of the winners the company that organizes Miss Universe   journalists , to sweat shirt and start a fight against weight|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the weight of Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.5896,
                    "answers": "weight|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "No doubt, Trump said.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say that No doubt, Trump said?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does ABC.es say about Trump?",
                    "score": 0.7911,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that No doubt , Trump said|ROOT\tthat|mark\tNo|neg\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did ABC.es say about Trump's claim?",
                    "score": 0.7778,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Trump and ABC?",
                    "score": 0.7075,
                    "answers": "No doubt|advmod\tthat No doubt , Trump said|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does ABC.es stand for?",
                    "score": 0.6839,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This brutal attack plunged her into deep depression.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did the attack occur?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the cause of death of Connie Mack?",
                    "score": 0.7549,
                    "answers": "that This brutal attack plunged her into deep depression|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the person who committed the brutal attack on Connie Mack?",
                    "score": 0.7192,
                    "answers": "her|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the attack on Connie Mack and the deep depression?",
                    "score": 0.6731,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThis|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I was sick.. I had anorexia and bulimia for five years, told the Venezuelan in an interview with The New York Times last May.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say I was sick?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What symptoms did I have for five years?",
                    "answer": "anorexia and bulimia"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did the Venezuelan suffer from anorexia and bulimia?",
                    "score": 0.794,
                    "answers": "for five years|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Venezuelans tell The New York Times in 2017 about their illness?",
                    "score": 0.7851,
                    "answers": "in an interview with The New York Times last May|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the news that the Venezuelan was sick?",
                    "score": 0.6978,
                    "answers": "that I was sick|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of anorexia and bulimia?",
                    "score": 0.6858,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj\ton 25/09/2017|prep\tanorexia and bulimia|dobj\tbulimia|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between anorexia and bulimia?",
                    "score": 0.645,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that I was sick ..|ROOT\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\tsick|acomp\t..|punct\tI|nsubj\tI had anorexia and bulimia for five years , told the Venezuelan in an interview with The New York Times last May|ROOT\tand|cc\tfive|nummod\t,|punct\tthe|det\tan|det\twith The New York Times|prep\tThe|det\tNew|compound\tNew York|compound\tlast|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Machado also had to endure being ridiculed by referring to her as Miss Piggy (Miss Pig) and Miss Housekeeping (Miss Housewife) for being Latina.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What were Machado's nicknames?",
                    "answer": "Miss Piggy (Miss Pig) and Miss Housekeeping (Miss Housewife)"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Machado say about Miss Piggy and Miss Housekeeping?",
                    "score": 0.7936,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep\tthat Machado also had to endure being ridiculed by referring to her as Miss Piggy ( Miss Pig ) and Miss Housekeeping ( Miss Housewife ) for being Latina|ccomp\tbeing ridiculed by referring to her as Miss Piggy ( Miss Pig ) and Miss Housekeeping ( Miss Housewife ) for being Latina|xcomp\tto her|prep\tfor being Latina|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Machado do to be ridiculed?",
                    "score": 0.788,
                    "answers": "to endure being ridiculed by referring to her as Miss Piggy ( Miss Pig ) and Miss Housekeeping ( Miss Housewife ) for being Latina|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Miss Housekeeping?",
                    "score": 0.6739,
                    "answers": "Miss Housekeeping ( Miss Housewife )|conj\tMiss Housewife|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Alicia Machado and Donald Trump in - ABCTrump had no objection to recognizing that he was pushing her to lose weight, arguing that keeping her in excellent shape was her obligation as Miss Universe.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who had no objection to recognizing that Donald Trump was pushing Alicia Machado to lose weight?",
                    "answer": "Alicia Machado and Donald Trump"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Trump and Alicia Machado?",
                    "score": 0.7232,
                    "answers": "keeping her in excellent shape|csubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the weight of Miss Universe Alicia Machado?",
                    "score": 0.7104,
                    "answers": "weight|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Democrat contender Hillary Clinton took Machado out as a visible face of Trump's macho attitude during the first presidential debate.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What happened during the first presidential debate?",
                    "answer": "Hillary Clinton took Machado out as a visible face of Trump's macho attitude"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Hillary Clinton say about Trump's macho attitude?",
                    "score": 0.8127,
                    "answers": "as a visible face of Trump 's macho attitude|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Machado say to Trump during the first debate?",
                    "score": 0.8124,
                    "answers": "out|prt"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Machado and Trump?",
                    "score": 0.6828,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tDemocrat contender|compound\tHillary|compound\tDemocrat contender Hillary Clinton|nsubj\ta|det\tvisible|amod\tof Trump 's macho attitude|prep\tthe|det\tpresidential|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Far from retreating, the Republican continued to attack Machado, who last summer obtained U.S. citizenship.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did the ABC say Machado was attacking Machado?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Machado do to gain US citizenship?",
                    "score": 0.8024,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Far from retreating , the Republican continued to attack Machado , who last summer obtained U.S. citizenship|ROOT\tFar|advmod\tFar from retreating|prep\tretreating|pcomp\tthe Republican|nsubj\tthat Far from retreating , the Republican continued to attack Machado , who last summer obtained U.S. citizenship|ccomp\tto attack Machado , who last summer obtained U.S. citizenship|xcomp\tlast|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Machado's citizenship?",
                    "score": 0.7603,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tMachado , who last summer obtained U.S. citizenship|dobj\twho|nsubj\twho last summer obtained U.S. citizenship|relcl\tU.S. citizenship|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Machado and Trump?",
                    "score": 0.6885,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep\t,|punct\tthe|det\tto|aux\t,|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Did corrupt Clinton help disgusting Alicia M?.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.abc.es say on 25/09/2017?",
                    "answer": "Did corrupt Clinton help disgusting Alicia M?"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Clinton do to corrupt Alicia M?",
                    "score": 0.8766,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Did corrupt Clinton help disgusting Alicia M ?|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Clinton and Alicia M?",
                    "score": 0.8136,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tDid|aux\tcorrupt|amod\tcorrupt Clinton|nsubj\tthat Did corrupt Clinton help disgusting Alicia M|ccomp\tAlicia|compound\tdisgusting Alicia M|dobj\t?|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "to become an American citizen to be able to use it in the debate?, Trump asked himself in a tweet.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Trump ask himself in a tweet on 25/09/2017?",
                    "answer": "to become an American citizen to be able to use it in the debate?,"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Trump tweet about becoming an American citizen?",
                    "score": 0.8358,
                    "answers": "a tweet|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the benefits of becoming a citizen of the United States?",
                    "score": 0.7055,
                    "answers": "able to use it in the debate|acomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Over the past few months, Alicia defended Clinton to an extreme extent.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who defended Clinton to an extreme extent?",
                    "answer": "Alicia"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did Alicia defend Clinton?",
                    "score": 0.891,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\t,|punct\tto an extreme extent|prep\tan|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many times has Alicia defended Clinton?",
                    "score": 0.8684,
                    "answers": "that Over the past few months , Alicia defended Clinton to an extreme extent|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Alicia and Clinton?",
                    "score": 0.7456,
                    "answers": "Over the past few months|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "On Wednesday, after learning about the nightmare of defeat, she contacted her via telephone to express her support.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How did www.abc.es contact her after learning of the nightmare of defeat?",
                    "answer": "via telephone"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the outcome of the election?",
                    "score": 0.6508,
                    "answers": "of defeat|prep\tdefeat|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the dream of defeat?",
                    "score": 0.6433,
                    "answers": "the nightmare of defeat|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Hillary Clinton's support for her campaign?",
                    "score": 0.6075,
                    "answers": "her support|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Hillary Clinton and the nightmare of defeat?",
                    "score": 0.6004,
                    "answers": "that On Wednesday , after learning about the nightmare of defeat , she contacted her via telephone to express her support|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I talked to her, she thanked me for supporting her in this campaign.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say that they talked to her?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the person who supported Hillary Clinton in the 2016 election?",
                    "score": 0.6478,
                    "answers": "her|pobj\tme|dobj\tsupporting her in this campaign|pcomp\ther|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the ABC campaign?",
                    "score": 0.6174,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I came by chance, and I'm still very firm with my position, he told Televisa.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say he came by chance?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Televisa say about his position?",
                    "score": 0.6807,
                    "answers": "by chance|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Trump and Televisa?",
                    "score": 0.6484,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep\tthat I came by chance , and I 'm still very firm with my position|ccomp\tI 'm still very firm with my position|conj\tvery firm with my position|acomp\twith my position|prep\tmy|poss\tmy position|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Televisa's position?",
                    "score": 0.5915,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Trump's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants also scotched on many of the beauty queens of Latin origin.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Trump's comments on Mexican immigrants do to beauty queens of Latin origin?",
                    "answer": "xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants also scotched on many of the beauty queens"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Trump say about the beauty queens of Latin origin?",
                    "score": 0.8023,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep\tTrump 's|poss\tthat Trump 's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants also scotched on many of the beauty queens of Latin origin|ccomp\tbeauty|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are Trump's comments on Mexican immigrants?",
                    "score": 0.7812,
                    "answers": "Trump 's xenophobic comments on Mexican immigrants|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Trump's stance on Mexican immigrants?",
                    "score": 0.7444,
                    "answers": "on Mexican immigrants|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Trump's comments on immigrants?",
                    "score": 0.7107,
                    "answers": "xenophobic|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Lupita Jones, former Miss Universe of Mexico, announced that her country would not participate in .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did Lupita Jones announce that her country would not participate in the Miss Universe?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Jones say about the Miss Universe of Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.8176,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Lupita Jones , former Miss Universe of Mexico , announced that her country would not participate in|ROOT\tthat|mark\tformer|amod\tformer Miss Universe of Mexico|appos\tthat Lupita Jones , former Miss Universe of Mexico , announced that her country would not participate in|ccomp\tthat|mark\ther|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Jones's participation in the Miss Universe competition?",
                    "score": 0.7578,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep\tthat her country would not participate in|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the US and Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.6464,
                    "answers": "of Mexico|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Former Miss Universe Zuleyka Rivera of Puerto Rico retired from the Miss USA jury.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who retired from the Miss USA jury?",
                    "answer": "Zuleyka Rivera"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did Zuleyka Rivera leave the Miss USA jury?",
                    "score": 0.8949,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Former Miss Universe Zuleyka Rivera of Puerto Rico retired from the Miss USA jury|ROOT\tthat|mark\tthat Former Miss Universe Zuleyka Rivera of Puerto Rico retired from the Miss USA jury|ccomp\tfrom the Miss USA jury|prep\tthe Miss USA jury|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Zuleyka Rivera?",
                    "score": 0.7598,
                    "answers": "Zuleyka|compound\tFormer Miss Universe Zuleyka Rivera of Puerto Rico|nsubj\tof Puerto Rico|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Zuleyka Rivera and Miss USA?",
                    "score": 0.7509,
                    "answers": "Puerto|compound\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "USA.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.abc.es say that the USA was in the US?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does ABC.es stand for?",
                    "score": 0.5794,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between USA and USA?",
                    "score": 0.5594,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "and the Colombian Paulina Vega, Miss Universe , called her speech unfair and harmful.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was Paulina Vega's title?",
                    "answer": "Miss Universe"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Paulina Vega say about Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.8179,
                    "answers": "Miss Universe|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "However, not all of them whipped up their godfather.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did not all of them do?",
                    "answer": "whipped up their godfather"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a father and a father?",
                    "score": 0.6379,
                    "answers": "up|prt"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete closed ranks around the owner of the contest.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who closed ranks around the owner of the contest?",
                    "answer": "Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was the owner of the Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete contest?",
                    "score": 0.7648,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Miss Universo Mexicana Ximena Navarrete closed ranks around the owner of the contest|ROOT\tthat|mark\tUniverso|compound\tranks|dobj\taround the owner of the contest|prep\tthe|det\tthe|det\tthe contest|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "My working relationship with Trump has always been very good.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.abc.es say that my working relationship with Trump has always been very good?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Trump and Baldwin?",
                    "score": 0.8266,
                    "answers": "working|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Trump's relationship with ABC?",
                    "score": 0.8164,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tMy|poss\tMy working relationship with Trump|nsubj\twith Trump|prep\thas|aux\talways|advmod\tthat My working relationship with Trump has always been very good|ccomp\tvery|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I can't tell you if he did wrong or well, he deserves all my respect.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say he couldn't tell you if he did wrong or well?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does ABC.es say about Trump?",
                    "score": 0.7636,
                    "answers": "all my respect|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the person who was accused of wrong or well received by ABC News?",
                    "score": 0.6168,
                    "answers": "n't|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did ABC.es say about the claim?",
                    "score": 0.5855,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the president and the person who committed the act?",
                    "score": 0.5769,
                    "answers": "if he did wrong or well , he deserves all my respect|advcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Those who did take letters in the matter after the attack on the Mexicans were the NBC networks, which cancelled the transmission of the contest, and Univision and Televisa who also broke professional ties with him.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Which networks broke professional ties with the Mexicans?",
                    "answer": "Univision and Televisa"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did Univision and Televisa break ties with Trump?",
                    "score": 0.7911,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep\tthat|mark\twho|nsubj\tdid|aux\tin the matter|prep\tthe|det\tthe matter|pobj\tafter the attack on the Mexicans|prep\tthe|det\ton the Mexicans|prep\tthe|det\tthe Mexicans|pobj\tthe|det\tthe NBC networks , which cancelled the transmission of the contest , and Univision and Televisa who also broke professional ties with him|attr\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\twhich cancelled the transmission of the contest|relcl\tthe|det\tthe transmission of the contest|dobj\tof the contest|prep\tthe|det\tthe contest|pobj\t,|punct\tand|cc\tand|cc\twho|nsubj\talso|advmod\twith him|prep\thim|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Univision and Televisa do after the attack on Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.6835,
                    "answers": "that Those who did take letters in the matter after the attack on the Mexicans were the NBC networks , which cancelled the transmission of the contest , and Univision and Televisa who also broke professional ties with him|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the NBC networks say about the attack on Mexicans?",
                    "score": 0.6833,
                    "answers": "the attack on the Mexicans|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Univision and Televisa?",
                    "score": 0.5956,
                    "answers": "letters in the matter|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In September , still a Republican candidate, sold the company that organizes Miss Universe to the entertainment event company WME/IMG.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "In what month and year did the company that organizes Miss Universe sell to WME/IMG?",
                    "answer": "September"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the company that organized Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.6644,
                    "answers": "Miss|compound\tWME|nmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between WME and Miss Universe?",
                    "score": 0.5913,
                    "answers": "that|mark\t,|punct\tstill|advmod\ta|det\t,|punct\tthat|nsubj\t/|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is WME/IMG?",
                    "score": 0.5236,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep\tIn September|prep\tthat In September , still a Republican candidate , sold the company that organizes Miss Universe to the entertainment event company WME / IMG|ccomp\tthe|det\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is WME/IMG?",
                    "score": 0.5195,
                    "answers": "In September , still a Republican candidate|advcl\tthe company that organizes Miss Universe|dobj\tthat organizes Miss Universe|relcl\tto the entertainment event company WME / IMG|prep\tentertainment|compound\tentertainment event|compound\tthe entertainment event company WME / IMG|pobj\tWME / IMG|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "ABC has tried to get in touch with them, but they have declined to make any statement about Trump.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did ABC say they had tried to get in touch with them?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did ABC say about Trump?",
                    "score": 0.852,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tany statement about Trump|dobj\tabout Trump|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between ABC and ABC?",
                    "score": 0.6776,
                    "answers": "in touch with them|prep\ttouch with them|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Surprisingly, the transaction took place only three days after the mogul bought from the NBC chain the part that did not yet own that company, becoming the sole owner.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take for the transaction to take place?",
                    "answer": "three days"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take for NBC to buy a part of NBC chain?",
                    "score": 0.7728,
                    "answers": "after|mark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who owns the NBC chain?",
                    "score": 0.7279,
                    "answers": "the part that did not yet own that company|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between ABC and NBC?",
                    "score": 0.6535,
                    "answers": "becoming the sole owner|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between NBC and ABC?",
                    "score": 0.6323,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tSurprisingly|advmod\t,|punct\tthe|det\tplace|dobj\tonly|advmod\tthe|det\tfrom the NBC chain|prep\tthe|det\tthe NBC chain|pobj\tthe|det\tthat|nsubj\tdid|aux\tnot|neg\tyet|advmod\tthat did not yet own that company|relcl\tthat|det\tthat company|dobj\t,|punct\tthe|det\tsole|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the sole owner of ABC?",
                    "score": 0.5954,
                    "answers": "the sole owner|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I enjoyed being the owner of the Miss Universe, Miss USA.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say that I enjoyed being the owner of the Miss Universe, Miss USA?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who owns Miss Universe, Miss USA?",
                    "score": 0.8419,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that I enjoyed being the owner of the Miss Universe , Miss USA|ROOT\tthat|mark\tI|nsubj\tthat I enjoyed being the owner of the Miss Universe , Miss USA|ccomp\tthe|det\tof the Miss Universe , Miss USA|prep\tthe|det\tMiss|compound\tthe Miss Universe , Miss USA|pobj\t,|punct\tMiss|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "U.S. and Miss Teen USA.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What country did the ABC say was the same as Miss Teen USA?",
                    "answer": "U.S."
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between US and Miss Teen USA?",
                    "score": 0.7656,
                    "answers": "that U.S. and Miss Teen USA|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Miss Teen USA?",
                    "score": 0.7537,
                    "answers": "Miss|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "USA.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.abc.es say that the USA was in the US?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does ABC.es stand for?",
                    "score": 0.5794,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between USA and USA?",
                    "score": 0.5594,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "When I got them, they were in serious trouble.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say they were in serious trouble?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the FBI and the Department of Homeland Security?",
                    "score": 0.6032,
                    "answers": "serious|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the group that was in serious trouble?",
                    "score": 0.5996,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that When I got them , they were in serious trouble|ROOT\ton 25/09/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tWhen|advmod\tI|nsubj\tthem|dobj\t,|punct\tthey|nsubj\tthat When I got them , they were in serious trouble|ccomp\tin serious trouble|prep\tserious trouble|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It has been an honor to make them a world success, he said in a statement.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.abc.es say it has been an honor to make them a world success?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to make them a world success?",
                    "score": 0.811,
                    "answers": "to make them a world success|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the organization that is known for being a world success?",
                    "score": 0.7101,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of all the quotes from Trump about the ABC program?",
                    "score": 0.7018,
                    "answers": "a statement|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does ABC.es stand for?",
                    "score": 0.6727,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Trump turned away from beauty competitions to take on a much more ambitious new job; leading the most powerful country in the universe.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did abc.es say that Trump turned away from beauty competitions to take on a more ambitious new job?",
                    "answer": "25/09/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did Trump turn away from beauty competitions?",
                    "score": 0.8445,
                    "answers": "www.abc.es said on 25/09/2017 that Trump turned away from beauty competitions to take on a much more ambitious new job ; leading the most powerful country in the universe|ROOT\tthat Trump turned away from beauty competitions to take on a much more ambitious new job ; leading the most powerful country in the universe|ccomp\taway from beauty competitions|advmod\tfrom beauty competitions|prep\tbeauty competitions|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What new job did Trump take from beauty competitions in 2017?",
                    "score": 0.8084,
                    "answers": "much more ambitious|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Trump's new job?",
                    "score": 0.7179,
                    "answers": "to take on a much more ambitious new job ; leading the most powerful country in the universe|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Trump and beauty competition?",
                    "score": 0.7004,
                    "answers": "on 25/09/2017|prep\tmost powerful|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the new job that Trump turned away from?",
                    "score": 0.6829,
                    "answers": "new|amod"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}